<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joint Insights</title>
    <link>http://jointinsights.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joint Insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 21:45:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jointinsights.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Joint Insights</title>
      <link>http://jointinsights.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 21:45:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jointinsights.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Why?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the mission of Joint Insights to help people leverage different perspectives and new approaches to connect with what matters most in their situation and solve the challenges they are facing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;How?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;focus-on-next-level-problems:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Focus on next-level problems&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you solve one problem, you expose the next one.  Embrace that, and constantly seek to find out what the root issue is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;write-the-dictionary:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Write the dictionary&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always baseline understanding.  Train and explain as necessary before applying a concept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;focus-on-problems-not-symptoms:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Focus on problems, not symptoms&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are often likely discussing symptoms.  If that&amp;rsquo;s all we solve, the problem doesn&amp;rsquo;t go away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;nourish-transparency:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Nourish transparency&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brutal truth puts us on the same page, and is most effective on moving us together in the same direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;who:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Who?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joint Insights is owned and operated by Rich Visotcky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://jointinsights.com/img/profile.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rich is a seasoned agile trainer and coach, bringing years of experience in helping hundreds of people learn agile concepts and put them into practice in their daily work and lives.  Rich loves to help connect people with the principles behind leaner, agile processes and practices so they build elastic skills and can adapt their approach as the problems they are faced with change.  He has a background in software development, having put to practice what he preaches.  Constantly at the intersection between those who want something done and those who want to do good work, Rich helps to bridge the gaps in communications between all.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>